# ŁUKASZ KUPŚ

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Web Developer with 10 years of experience, focused on Front-end side of the development process. I love creating nice and useful things for the Internet people.

In my spare time I love to read sci-fi books, do some jogging, work on side-projects, write tech articles on personal website or learn how to create my own indie game :)

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScriptES6(experienced)

Vue.js / Vuex (experienced)

Git (experienced)

Unit Testing (Mocha, Chai, Jest) (intermediate)

Express.js (intermediate)

Node.js (intermediate)

Wordpress (intermediate)

PhoneGap / Cordova mobile development (intermediate)

TypeScript (intermediate)

Meteor.js (beginner)

Angular.js 1.x (beginner)

React.js (beginner)

Experienced in working with provided backend services built with Ruby On Rails, Django or Node.js frameworks. Working in Agile methodologies.

## **WORK HISTORY**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT MERCEDES-BENZ.IO (REMOTE)

02/2021 - currently

Creating internal MVP application using Vue.js + TypeScript + internal framework.

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT HICX SOLUTIONS (REMOTE)

02/2020 - currently

Maintaining company product, developing new functionalities using Vue.js framework.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT UPSTACK.CO (REMOTE)

02/2020 - currently

Contract / freelance front-end development via Upstack platform.

#### **FULL-STACK FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER (REMOTE)**

01/2015 – currently

A-Z web development from UI design to the deployment on client's server. Working on side-projects that automate everyday programming tasks.

Using Node.js, JavaScript, Vue.js, Express.js, Webpack, Gulp.js, Brunch.js, Sass, git.

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT QCONTACT (REMOTE)

01/2018 - 02/2020

Front-end development of SaaS application for communication. Using Vue.js, WebRTC, SIP, Webpack, Mocha, Chai, Jest, git

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT INFLUENSTER (REMOTE)

06/2017 - 10/2017

Maintaining company product, rebuilt main application module (search) from Django template based to React.js one.

## JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER AT ITM BUSINESS SP. Z O.O. (POZNAN, POLAND)

04/2015 - 04/2017

Maintenance and further development of internal front-end framework, creating web applications and Single Page Apps based on company's product API. Developing mobile applications based on already created web modules. Using JavaScript, jQuery, PhoneGap, Cordova, bits of Angular.js 1.x, git.

## WEB DEVELOPER AT ITM BUSINESS SP. Z O.O. SP. K. (POZNAN, POLAND)

10/2013 - 03/2015

Creating Wordpress and custom CMS based websites, development of front-end framework for ERP (SaaS) application. Using JavaScript, Wordpress, git.

## FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER, WEBRACKETS (REMOTE)

06/2010 - 11/2014

Creating Wordpress-based websites, slicing psd files to templates, front-end development.

## **EDUCATION**

## POZNAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (MASTER DEGREE: IT IN BUSINESS PROCESSES)

Thesis title: Development of Content Management System using Meteor.js – a Node.js framework.

## POZNAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (ENGINEER DEGREE: COMPUTER SCIENCE)

BsC Thesis title: *Implementing personal data generator for testing purposes in Ruby on Rails framework.* 

Page | 2 Łukasz Kupś

# OTHER RESOURCES

# LINKEDIN

https://linkedin.com/in/lukaszkups

# **GITHUB**

https://github.com/lukaszkups

# **TWITTER**

https://twitter.com/lukaszkups

# **BLOG**

https://lukaszkups.net/notes

Page | 3 Łukasz Kupś